[Music]
all right so it's part two of Guru
versus student we got Jordan Jordan is
pulling up right now so in the last
competition Jordan won uh the
competition ten thousand dollars you
guys are about to see why we just did
this why we just shaved our heads but
this is part two so make sure you guys
watch all the video to the end because
there's a lot of exciting things coming
and very educational because we're about
to teach both of our strategies how we
go about it in a week
yo you got the ten thousand right
huh you got the ten thousand
what's up
bro how are you gonna tell me you lost
to your student Jordan at all I mean
yeah and actually I didn't expect that
but I'm coming for blood this time I'm
not playing any games
[Applause]
Jordan won the last competition and we
ran a little competition this week which
whoever loses had to shave their head
it's clear who lost
[Music]
so does it have a following I have to
lead by example everything that I
practice I preach so if I made Jordan go
through this
it's only right if I do it so go
[Music]
[Applause]
no no it's not too bad
wow
[Music]
all right so you know we just had to
shave our head bro because we lost the
bat but Jordan had to do it to lead by
example but now we're gonna take him to
the club we got the boy tiny with us
we're gonna tell him what's up we got to
go is Jordan with us
so Jordan uh Jordan's never gone out to
a club so it's his first time going out
and then he's gonna be driving around
time
oh
[Music]
all right so no trade so far today on
Monday we already did the madnesses
we're away from some setups that I think
that should play out by probably Tuesday
Wednesday but this is going to be the
last time I ever do a three-day boot
camp you guys know I had the 333
whatever I don't like certain courses I
just like trading chilling and just you
know having fun and traveling but the
three-day was requested so much that I'm
doing no application no waiting list
just on Friday April 7th is going to be
the last time I ever do a three-day boot
camp you guys click the link below you
guys will see all the information there
it's going to be the last time I ever do
it I don't want to sell quarters anymore
I just want to trade and chill so if you
guys don't know more about it click the
link below last time doing it no
application no waiting list let's get on
with the video the first day of the
challenge I'll go over this trade real
quick so we're actually able to catch
two percent today on Monday so we're
already up Alex has to put in some work
this week I was able to catch this cell
even though your USD is bullish on a
higher time frame so if we go to each
one real quick notice this this big push
to the downside look at this big bearish
volume coming into the downside and then
notice this previous contrary candle
right here that gives the push to the
downside this is our supply and then
notice as soon as New York opened check
this out as soon as New York opened let
me put my session volume so you can see
notice how we touch this area Supply
right here notice how we touched her
here we touched it again and then we got
volume to the balance that we create a
new area of Supply on M1 so this is our
M1 confirmation to enter off of this
bigger time frame Zone So I entered
right here with my stop loss eight Pips
how I always usually do and then you can
see we caught a very nice one to two and
if you notice notice for Price respected
here it's not a very it's not a random
area if we go to M5 notice this area of
demand where price respected
um almost respected you can see we make
it look like that it almost touched it
but you can see this is the area where
price pulled back to this M5 Demand
right here but yeah guys this was an
easy super simple trade H1 Supply M1
confirmation but yeah let's see what
happens tomorrow
this Tuesday morning is the second day
of the challenge and I'm gonna show you
guys what I'm looking at for a New York
session today so this is your USD on the
weekly time frame so check this out guys
I'm gonna make this as simple as
possible notice this push that we had to
the downside you notice this previous
contrary candle this is this area of
Supply right here and so as soon as we
touch this area supply for like a month
and a half a little bit more we had a
bearish move so if we go to the Daily
time frame keep in mind this is a weekly
so if we go to the Daily notice this
area of Supply right here this previous
country candle that was created that
gave us this push once we touch this
weekly Supply now we have this daily
Supply right here so we have literally
have nothing touching price up until
this area and if we go to H4 to break it
down a little bit more notice how we're
literally 70 Pips away we have this
daily Supply right here and this um H4
Supply right here so just because we're
bullish on a higher time frame doesn't
mean that we're not going to have a
bearish movement for New York for
example yesterday we sold and we're in a
bear in a bullish Market because that's
where we're presented for the session
for example we're bullish but for when
we came to trade for New York session we
had a bearish movement so we sold so
today's probably going to be the same
thing we're probably going to see price
break above these highs right here and
then give us a pull back to the downside
so that's what I'm anticipating for
today's session all right so now we got
the bag secured for the day honestly
we're getting into the week because I
was two percent plus yesterday's two
percent honestly Alex has gonna have to
put some words to catch up but now we
got the bag secured we're gonna get on
with our day we're gonna go get a
haircut get something to eat and then
hit the gym all right so this day two of
the competition it is currently Tuesday
March 21st pre-london so earlier today
in the morning I was trading live on
Rocket 21's YouTube channel so I
actually live streamed for the first
time ever on their Channel and then this
is what I was predicting for AUD USD all
we need is for price to come back into
this area give me a one hour bearish
engulfing or even a Candlestick like
this on the four hour it would be
beautiful
a rejection Candlestick if not we wait
for the next trade at the retest here of
the EMA and the structure to go to the
downside so I'm going to show you guys
an update of how the market is playing
out exactly from what I was predicting
earlier this morning and for what I'm
expecting to happen during uh London
tonight because I haven't taken any
trades so far this week Monday no trades
Tuesday morning earlier on the stream no
trades so let's see if we can get a
trade tonight in London so this is what
I'm looking at this right here is what
I'm looking at currently on
AUD USD you guys can tell this is the
pair that we were trading earlier on the
live stream because you guys can tell
like I mentioned earlier we are
obviously bearish on the higher time
frames we are pulling up to a solid
daily area of Interest which is right
here we're rejecting this level of
support being used as resistance
beautiful daily bearish engulfing I just
don't like how we are pulling up to that
structure level and we closed above it
but when you go down to the lower time
frames like the four hour you guys can
tell right here we are on the four hour
time frame we're having a beautiful
retest of this neckline of The Head and
Shoulders retest of the EMA and then all
I'm going to be waiting for now is on
the lower time frames like the one hour
to have a like I need like a bearish
engulfing Candlestick rejection from
this Zone rejection from the EMA
rejection from around psychological and
uh a bearish engulfing should be a solid
entry signal and then I'll probably have
my stop so if I take the trail let's say
like the candle in golf somewhere around
here I'll probably have my stops around
here and I'll keep my take profit to the
same daily low so little trick for you
guys if you're setting off a daily area
of interest you got to set a daily take
profit so my daily tape profit would be
to the structure level here giving me
about a one to four risk to reward so if
I risk two percent on this trade and
this trade hits that's literally my
eight percent
you could pass any challenge or eight
percent all right so it's currently
about a couple hours out from London so
people ask me all the time like what do
you do how do you stay up for London so
we're gonna warm up some food right now
and usually I'll eat around this time
and this sounds kind of crazy but
literally every single hour that I stay
up so I watch every single Candlestick
right so I set an alarm because I'm a
very deep sleeper so I'll put an alarm
every single hour so I'll put one at one
put one at two three up to four in the
morning and every single time the alarm
rings I literally just wake up I look at
trading you like one eye I look at it
like this if it hasn't give me my my
entry signal I just fall right back
asleep wait for the next hour I
literally fall back asleep in like 30
seconds
um and then that way if I get my entry
stick my entry Candlestick I enter the
trade because I only enter candlesticks
at the closure of the candle so it's
like a little hack to my style so we're
gonna eat some food and then see if we
catch the trade uh later tonight I told
you what's gonna happen is what ended up
happening in this session so check this
out I told you it was very likely price
was going to break above these highs
manipulate and then give the
distribution to the downside you can see
that's literally what happened price
pulled back to this area right here this
previous contrary candle which is the
true aerial supplier demand and then
notice to the exact pip literally to the
PIP price activator or orders and then
went to the downside I actually did call
this in the signal group so check this
out guys let me let me break this down
for you even more so if you go to on M5
you can see it perfect notice how
this is very equal like this it looks
like a perfect area of supply and I said
this in my story I was like when I first
started trading I would have seen this
and would have got desperate as soon as
New York opened I would have started
selling which as you can see as soon as
New York opened everybody was sitting
right here because it looks like a
perfect area Supply but what ends up
happening is price will break above it
like manipulate Above This accumulation
and then get the distribution and then
when the price pulls back to the
previous country candle that is the
entry right there so yes guys this was a
trade right here we caught a nice one to
two so far we're up four percent for the
week so let's see what's going on with
Alex all right so the bag is secured
guys we got the Smoothie we gym now
we're gonna go back home go over the
charts and then go for a walk with Tommy
so it's the third day of the challenge
today is Wednesday morning and I'm gonna
break down what I expect to see for New
York session this morning Alex better to
have something cooking because we are
2-0 this week we are up four percent so
far today is the third uh trading day
but honestly if I were to call it a week
like we're still at four percent so
that's pretty solid so let's just get
right into it so
um first things first notice how pretty
New York this area of Supply was created
pushing this volume to the downside and
pretty much we're presented with the
same situation as
uh Monday and Tuesday we're in a bullish
Market but for New York session we're
having a bearish momentum which we're
having a pullback notice uh Monday we
sold because out is what literally was
presented for us and then Tuesday again
as well and then today again as well
notice how we have this volume coming
down M15 Supply
M5 Supply so I have my cell limit placed
literally right here but on the higher
time frame there's literally nothing
stopping price if we look if we go to H4
real quick
there is nothing stopping price up until
this area right here which is about 30
Pips away I mean
um no about 50 Pips away but the thing
is we trade what's presented so what's
presented is this cell movement so we're
gonna see what happens
all right guys so it's Wednesday right
now March 22nd so still no trade so far
um I was supposed to take a trade
earlier today in the morning luckily I
did I'm gonna pop it up right here we
got Wicked out and we would have taken
it so now we're hitting the gym right
now we're with Kevin these are the guys
that they wrapped my car we got mail
over there
[Music]
so still no trade so far but we'll see
you later tonight in London if we get
one and now we'll have one tomorrow
always making games run all right so we
just got home right now from the gym and
my look I'm not putting up my I'm like
sword [__] right so I'm gonna show you
guys right now exactly on the trade that
we were going to take earlier and we
didn't because I followed my training
plan and I'm gonna I'm just gonna
explain to you guys why right so this
right here it is USD Kai so USD CAD
pretty much we were looking for the buy
uh once we broke this structure level
above here so this is the structure
level if you noticed this was uh my
alarm so once we broke it I was waiting
for the pullback and then the entry
around this level but I literally
explained this in my free telegram so
here in my free telegram I sent the
trader idea I'm like trade idea possible
strong rejection this air and interest
waiting a little bit more if you notice
here I hadn't taken it because it was
under my area of interest and then here
how I explained how patience avoided for
me to take this loss so if you notice
here on this area we have the area of
interest that we were supposed to buy
but we were under it so my number one
rule is we need two time time frames in
sync to take the trade if you notice we
have the weekly and the daily and then
my second Confluence is that we need to
buy a bowl of support or sell under
resistant very simple right and in this
case we were under the under the the
support so you notice this right here
was being used as resistance so we we
would have bought we were literally
buying straight into resistance so we
did not take the trade if we would have
we would have literally been Wicked out
which kind of sucks I love how the daily
Candlestick has closed right now they
have a beautiful daily bullish pin bar
so I'm going to remain sticking to my
rules and I'm just going to Simply wait
for the retest Above This zone right
here literally what I have drawn right
here wait for the reasons Above This
Zone to take the trade at the buy so I
update you guys tomorrow major trouble
because literally exactly what I told
you guys was going to happen is what
ended up happening so check this out
notice how price as soon as uh New York
opened up we pulled back to this M5
Supply that I told you guys which is
also M15 Supply there and Confluence and
then notice how I called the Solomon
actually in the signal group so notice
how as soon as the Solomon hit we went
well we went up almost most two times
our risk uh literally a few Pips away
from tp2 and then now price pull back
into the to the entry and then now we're
still in profit right now I'm not gonna
lie on break even so if price takes me
out right now I'm still four percent for
the week and I'm break even if price
hits my take profit I would be up six
percent for the week and we're only
three days in so Alex literally has some
work to do if not I see him losing this
challenge but exactly how I told you
guys this M5 Supply notice we pulled
back in here and then that's where the
movement came in from
so far I'm up four percent if we could
catch a solid trade today or tomorrow
then we'll definitely take it but let me
show you guys what I'm looking at for
New York session today so real quick let
me just try to do a quick breakdown for
you guys so notice how on the weekly
time frame on Euro USD we created this
bearish move to the downside and then
this previous contrary candle is our
supply right here notice how we pulled
back touched it and then we got a
bearish move for a few weeks so keeping
that in mind if we go to H1 let me show
you guys this
uh I know it looks very tiny right now
but look check this out it's very
specific so notice how we touch this
weekly Supply
um we touched the weekly Supply this is
H1 and then we created this H1 Supply
right here this previous contrary candle
that gave us the push coming out of the
weekly Supply and then notice how last
night during London we touched this area
to the PIP notice how we touch it to the
PIP and then we got this bearish move to
the downside so if we go to M15
notice this after touching this H1
Supply last night we created this M15
Supply that gave us this move right here
this strong move to the downside so very
likely New York is going to pull back to
this area to continue the cell movement
so that's what I'm anticipating this
morning very likely the cells
[Applause]
opportunity was presented during New
York session I was telling you guys that
I was anticipating price to pull back to
this M15 M5 Supply that was created
after we touched the initial H1 Supply
up here and then you can see that price
pulled back but we didn't touch it
exactly by seven Pips so maybe tonight
uh price will pull back into this area
to continue the cells but as you can see
prices did not touch my zone so I'm not
going to chase after price I literally
I'm very disciplined with how I enter
the market and since no opportunity was
presented I didn't force the trade we're
still four percent for the week and we
start tomorrow left so we'll see what
happens all right guys so it is Friday
morning so we're literally about to lead
to New York meeting group and um I'm
just going to show you guys this real
quick
but
do you guys remember the trade that I
was explaining to you guys that I wanted
to catch
we are currently up
42 000 on the trade I'm gonna show you
guys exactly what I was waiting for
how I took it why I took it literally
right before we leave to New York right
now everybody got picked up my first
time on a jet
I'm kind of nervous not gonna lie
um I've always wanted to take a jet so I
finally was able to Target one all right
so you guys remember that I was looking
at this trade right here USD CAD we are
now on the one hour time frame kind of
how I was explaining to you guys earlier
I look for my entries on the one hour so
this trade right here was sent
everywhere free telegram
um students in the Discord already know
what's the deal because I break these
down every single week with them so you
break it down every single week right so
we already know that the majority of the
time frames were bullish and then we
were waiting for the break of this
structure level so this is where I go
down to the lower time frames and I'm
literally I hate when people say oh all
you do is wait for a break and retest
but it's like bro what more do you need
like right now I'm currently up on this
trade a one to three one to three point
three and then I'm having my take profit
based off of a daily structure point
because if I'm buying at a daily area of
Interest which is this point right here
we are buying it at this daily structure
point right here so currently right now
I but I might hold throughout the
weekend but what I think next week is
going to do I think we're going to have
a higher low so they continue going to
the upside so I don't want to hold
throughout the higher low and I don't
want to sell that high or low I want to
buy at this next higher low so I might
just get out at this four hour structure
point that we're pulling up to right
here to the left so next you're going to
dust pull back re-test this neckline of
the kind of the head and shoulders and
creates the higher low this right here
will be another potential buy
opportunity for me so it's really that
easy let me show you guys again one more
time how the trade is looking so the
trade we were up earlier about
43 000 now we're up about 42
000. so my little person I forget Friday
it's our last day of the challenge we're
up four percent so far if we could catch
a trade today then we'll end with six
seven percent maybe eight percent but to
be honest I don't want to force a trade
I'm going to show you guys what I'm what
we're working with I know let's break
down my help a lot of you guys so check
this out
um notice how yesterday I told you guys
if you remember I told you guys that I
wanted to sell right here I wanted to
press the pullback and sell from this
area here notice how price I didn't
touch this area by five Pips but notice
how that would have been the entry
literally to all this volume I don't
want to break down this cell because
it's not random so if we go to H1 real
quick notice this notice how we had this
bearish move right here but notice where
it's coming from it's coming from this
H1 Supply right here this previous
contrary candle that gave us this big
move right here notice how it gave us
this huge move to the downside and then
literally like a few weeks later here we
are touching it and then we touched it
exactly to the PIP and then you can see
that's where the bearish move came in
from and then you could tell now that
price we're pulling back from this H1
demand that we are at right now so if we
go around 15 real quick let me show you
what we're working with for today
actually let me go down five if we go to
M5 notice this notice how we touch this
area of Demand right here we touch it
and then on M5 we create this new area
Demand right here this new previous
country candle before this push we pull
back and you can see we're using it but
the thing is that we have important news
at 9 45 we have a red folder News so
what I'm anticipating is for price to
probably pull back more than likely to
this previous High update to continue
the sales from this area what I'm
honestly waiting for price to do is for
a lot of volume to come in at 9 45 I'm
guessing like price is just gonna pull
back to this area and then continue the
cells from this area that's just what
I'm anticipating price could just shoot
down and then obviously we're not going
to chase price but for me to enter price
I would have to see the volume like the
the volume from the news push price back
up to this area create a supply and then
continue the sales
yo this hella brick out here I think I
know what you guys say it's called as a
brick look at this this is a brick
we don't have this in my hand
bro I don't get it every single place we
go to whenever we go to visit for meet
and greets it's raining it's like we
bring the rain from Miami and I'm not
built for this coach
all right so we're here in the spot
right now we're gonna do the meet and
greet um we're just gonna start setting
things up really fast make sure
everything is good to go once the people
pull up we already have somebody waiting
here and the event is going to be at
seven o'clock and it is currently
two o'clock it is two o'clock right now
and then there's somebody already
waiting here four hours prior we're
gonna go say what's up to him
it's not built for this cold
all right so I pulled the party to the
venue make sure everything is good
another bowl and then another special
piece here from your wife
all right so about five minutes out from
starting the event sorry that I had to
you know make you guys wait outside it's
been cold and rainy but I promise you
it's going to be always an hour about to
start right now in five minutes I'll see
you guys tell them where you from
Jamaica Street you don't know big up
yard up top Alex
Gonzalez
yo LG thank you for coming we really
appreciate it and thank you for
everything forget bro
it's really hard about me I get it I
might have some materialistic things
that some of you guys might want to
achieve like the car the line with the
house and the watches all that is cool
but once I leave here tonight I just go
to that home by myself right like I
don't have a dog I have a goat once yeah
it's not in the back of Miami it's a
gentleman's game right so this week I
made about three percent only on that
one trade that it took pretty much on
Friday and Jordan made about four four
point five percent so I lost fair and
square so this is the ten thousand
dollars that I'm gonna
and now to my boy Jordan bro
here
so that's only ten thousand bro so I can
give you the ten thousand like wire uh I
could go withdraw cash crypto like
whatever you want
uh to be honest I was thinking to get a
wired sent by crypto and just deposit
into a broker and flip it I could even
make like a YouTube series out of it so
you're gonna you wanna be crypted to you
and then you flip it yeah I'll just
deposit until it broke flip 10K to like
what
that goes twenty thousand I think so it
does like 100 yeah and that's fire yeah
so then if you flip it then you just
give me the money back and then like
it's your money yeah
no but I'm not yeah that's far I mean
you guys saw here bro like Jordan was my
student
um he pretty much learned everything
made into his own style and now he's
having great success with it and to me
that he's having better results than me
makes me happy because it's like bro
what I was able to teach him he made
something out of it now he's having his
own result so I think that's what it's
all about so bro I want to thank you for
this competition I don't thank you for
taking my money but I uh if you guys
like this video make sure to drop like a
comment uh subscribe and then let me
know what you guys want to see for
another video or if we should do a part
three where we triple or nothing bro
I'll see you guys in the next one